The Register to the Betsy Jolas Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Correspondence, 1937-2010; Series II
  - Paper, 1
    - Atlantic Center for the Arts, 1990-1996; 4 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Attasch, Xavier, 1990; 1 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Aubier, Eric, 1996; 1 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Auric, Georges, 1967; 3 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      See also Académie du Disque Français
    - Autret, Fréderique, 1991; 2 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Aux Amateur de Livres (Librairie), 1983; 1 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - L'Avant Scène Opèra, 1977-1995; 3 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Averitt, Will, 1978-1987; 3 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Ayers, Lydia, 1989; 1 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Azria, Elie, No date; 1 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Bachman, Rhonda, 1980; 1 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Bacon, Alexis, 1997-1998; 8 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Baillet, Brigitte, 1978-1980; 5 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      See also photographs
    - Baker's Biographical Dictionary of Musicians, 1986-1995; 5 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Balissant, Jean, 2002; 2 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Ballif, Claude, 1981; 1 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Bamford, Alistair, 1995; 4 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Bancquart, A. and Marie-Claire, 1985-2002; 2 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Bancroft, Alan, 1996; 2 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Banda, Daniel, 1984; 2 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      See also Université de Paris I
    - Banff Centre for the Arts, 1989-1992; 5 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Barber, Valerie (Management), 1996; 1 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Barbizet, Pierre, 1959; 1 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Barclay Hoche Enregistrements, 1962; 1 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Bard Music Festival, 2001; 1 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Bärenreiter Verlag, 1964; 1 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Barraud, Dr. H.J., 1972; 1 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Barraud, Henri, 1949-1977; 3 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Barreau, Gisele, 1978-1993, no date; 20 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      See also Thomson, William
    - Barrois, Maïté, 1982; 1 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Baruch, Gerth-Wolfgang, 1970-1971; 14 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      See also Südwestfunk Baden-Baden
    - Le Barvoux, Tina, 1983; 2 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Baseman, Paul, 1995; 1 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Bataille-Lacan, Sylvia, 1993; 1 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      See also Lacan, Judith
    - Bath Festival, 1986; 2 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      See also United Music Publishers
    - Baulieu, Etienne, 1999; 2 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Baumgartner, Jean-Paul, 1968; 2 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Bauret-Allard Claude, 2010; 1 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Bayen, Bruno, 1988-2006, no date; 13 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      See also Éditions Salabert
    - Bayerischer Rundfunk, 1984; 2 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Bayle, François, 1993; 1 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Beaulieu, Etienne, No date; 1 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Bedenbaugh, Kay, 1981; 2 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Beecroft, Norma
      See New Music Concerts
    - Belgische Radio en Televisie (BRT), 1963; 2 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Bell, Millicent, 1986-2001; 28 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Belling, Susan, 1986-1989; 4 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Bello, Aurélien, 2007; 1 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Benbow, Charles, No date; 1 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Benjamin, George, 1984-2006; 11 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Benitez, Vincent P., 1982; 2 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Bentz, Thérese, 1993; 1 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Bennington College, 1977-1995; 15 (Box 25, Folder 12)
      See also Colem, Liz; Godwin, Becky; Siegel, Martha
    - Béranger, Vinciane, 1999; 2 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Bereau, Jean Sébastien, 1980; 1 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Bérely, Rachel, 2000; 1 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Beretti, Michel, 2000; 1 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Berio, Luciano, 1990-1996; 6 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      See also Groupe Instrumentale de Paris
    - Berio, Talia, 2003; 3 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Berleant, Andrea, 1986; 1 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Bernager, Olivia, No date; 1 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - ?, Bernard, 1966-2004 [?]; 3 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Bernard, Jean-Alphonse, 2000; 1 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Bernard, Kathleen, 1983; 2 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Bernard, Maurice, 1985-1991; 4 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      See also École Polytechnique
    - Bernède, Jean-Claude (and Roy, Madeleine), 1989; 1 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Bernstein, Giora, 1979-2002; 19 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      See also Colorado Music Festival; University of Colorado
    - Beroff, Christine, 1984; 1 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Bertagna, Louis, Dr., 1994; 1 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Bertrand, Juille, 1986; 1 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Bettelheim, Wilhelm, 1985; 1 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Bibliotheque Nationale (France), 1971, no date; 2 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Bickell, Paul, 1993; 2 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Bidou, Patrice, 1969; 7 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Biget, Michelle, 1988; 2 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Bingham, Sallie, 1987; 1 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      See also New York Public Library
    - Biography International, 1986; 1 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Biret, Idil, 1988; 1 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Bissiriex, Henri, 1960; 4 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Bitsch, Marcel, 1994; 2 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Blain, Lisette, 2004; 1 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Blake, Braxton, 1978-1979; 3 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Le Blanc Mesnil, 2003; 3 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Blank, William, No date; 1 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Blaustein, Susan (Suzy), 1980-1988; 3 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Bleuse, Marc
      See Conservatoire National Supérieur de Musique de Paris
    - Bloch, Thomas, 1983; 2 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Blocker, Robert L.
      See Yale University
    - Bloem, R., 1995; 1 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Blondeau, Thierry, 2001-2006; 3 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Boepple, Paul, 1946-1955; 36 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Boepple, Muriel, 1983; 4 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Bokser, Zelman, No date; 2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Boileau, Martine and Henri, 1983-2007, no date; 10 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Boivin, Jean, 1989-1996; 2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Bon, André, 1990-2007; 20 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      See also D'un Opéra de Voyage
    - Bonnet, Antoine, 1990-1994; 5 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Bonnet, Marie-Jo, 1993; 2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Boone, Charles, 1972; 2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Boone, Graeme, 1986; 1 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Boosey Hawkes, 1989; 1 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Bordas S.A., 1985-1991; 2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Bortoli, Georges, 1992; 1 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Bosse, Denis, 1988; 2 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Bosseur, Dominique, No date; 3 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Boston Symphony Orchestra, 1977-1998; 3 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      See also Gustin, Daniel R.; Tanglewood Music Center
    - Boston University, 1984-1995; 13 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      See also Theodore Presser Company
    - Botti, Susan, 2004; 1 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Boucher, Lisa Michelle, 1994; 1 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Bouchet, André du, 1961-1999; 15 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      See also Leduc, Jean
    - Bouchet, Gilles du, 1992-2004; 7 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Bouchet, Paule du, 1985, no date; 3 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Boucourechliev, André, 1961-1997; 38 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Bouillon, Vincent, 1988; 3 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Boulanger, Nadia, 1978-1979; 3 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Boulez, Pierre, 1959-2010; 27 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Bourdin, Roland, 1978-1989; 8 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Bourhis, Sophie, 1984; 1 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Bousch, François, 1991-1993; 5 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Boussac, Marc, 1966; 1 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Boutte, Tony, 2000; 1 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Boziwick, George E., 1984; 2 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Brabo, Michèle, 1989; 1 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Bracchi, Marta, 1984; 2 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Brant, Henry, 1969-1970; 5 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Bracquemond, Agnès (and ?, Beatrice), 1990-1999, no date; 9 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Braziller, George (Inc.), 1977; 2 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Breitkopf und Härtel Musikverlag, 1970; 2 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Breitman, Michel, 1984; 2 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Bresnick, Martin (and Lisa), 1982-2001; 16 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      See also Yale University
    - Briand, Luca, 1995; 2 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Brinkmann, Reinhold
      See Harvard University
    - Briscoe, James, 1985-1999; 19 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - British Broadcasting Corporation (BBC)
      See Isaacs, Jessica; United Music Publishers
    - Brockway, Thomas P., 1982-1983; 2 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Broido, Arnold P., 1973-1986; 3 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      See also Broido, Thomas; Heugel et Cie.; Theodore Presser Company
    - Broido, Thomas, 1989-1997; 21 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      See also Theodore Presser Company; Wajyma, Hiroko
    - Broman, Per, 1994; 2 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      See also Delangle, Claude
    - Brooks, William
      See University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign
    - Brossmann, Jean-Pierre, 1987-1999; 7 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      See also Erlo, Louis; Opéra de Lyon
    - Broude Brothers Limited, 1973; 2 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Brown, Earle, 1966-2000; 13 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Brown, Henry
      See Duo Parker Brown
    - Brown, Timothy, 1985; 1 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Brozak, Daniel, 1981; 3 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Brubeck, Iola, 1979; 1 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Bruneau, Marc Dr., 1996; 2 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - B. Schott's Söhne, 1964-1969; 2 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Buci-Glucksmann, Christine
      See L'Itineraire
    - Buirge, Susan, 1989; 1 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Bunn, David Alan, 1996; 3 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Burgan, Patrick, 1991; 1 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Burge, David, 1977; 4 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      See also Eastman School of Music
    - Burleson, Geoffrey, 2000; 1 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Buron, Gilles, 1989; 1 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Burns, Jeffrey, 1996-2000; 3 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Burns, Lori A.
    - Bussoti, Sylvano, 1986; 1 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Buttin, Véronique, No date; 1 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Cachin, Françoise, 1993[?]; 3 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Cadieu de Medina, Martine, 1977-1994; 2 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Cage, John, 1967; 2 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Caillat, Stéphane, 1974; 1 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Caillon, Christiane, 1996, no date; 3 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Caillot, Marc, 1984; 2 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Cajori, Marion, 1989-1990; 25 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Calabro, Louis
      See Sage City Symphony
    - California Institute of the Arts
      See England, Nicholas M.; Levine, Renée; Rosenboom, David
    - Caltabiano, Ronald, 1984; 1 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Cambreling, Sylvain, 1988; 2 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Camatte, Laurent, No date; 1 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Campana, José Luis, 1987-1988; 2 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Campion, Edmund, 1992; 2 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Campos, José Carlo, 1989; 6 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Campo, Régis, 1996-2003; 4 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Campogrande, Nicola, 1993; 2 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Campus Internazionale di Musica, 1995; 2 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Camus, Michel, 1991-1996; 3 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Canadian Cultural Centre, 1975-2004; 9 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Canadian Music Centre, 1974; 2 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Canadian Music Council
      See Huot, Guy
    - Canonici, Corrado, 1995-1996; 3 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Cantagrel, Gilles, No date; 2 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Carhart, David, 2002; 2 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Carl, Robert, 1980-1991 [?]; 5 (Box 26, Folder 10)
      See also Hartt School of Music
    - Carlson, Kent, 1992; 3 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Caroli, Mario, 2004; 1 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Princesse Caroline de Monaco, 1990-1992; 5 (Box 26, Folder 10)
      See also Monaco, Principauté de
    - Carrive, Paulette, 1986; 1 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Carroy, Jean-Roger, 1986; 1 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Carter, Elliott, 1976-1993; 17 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Carter, Helen, 1984; 1 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Cartier-Bresson, Henri, 1973-1993; 5 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Casadesus, Béatrice, 2002; 1 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Casadesus, Gaby, No date; 2 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Casadesus, Thérèse Rawson, 1997; 5 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Casino Municipal D'Aix-Thermal, 1966; 1 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Castanet, Pierre Albert, 1988-1993; 7 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Castarede, Marie-France (née Boutan), 1984, no date; 7 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Catherine, Susan, 1992; 1 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Castézède, Jacques, No date; 2 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Castro, Dino, 1970-1988; 6 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Cattseiu, David, 1992-1993; 5 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Caubisens, Paul, No date; 1 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Caussé, Gerard, 1988 [?]; 3 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Caussade, Simone Plé-, No date; 1 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Cavanna, Bernard, 2004; 1 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Cecconi-Botella, Monic, 1994; 2 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Cédric, Chanot, 2000; 2 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Cello Octet Conjunto Ibérico, No date; 1 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Centre d'Arts Contemporains, 1978-1988; 3 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Centre Culturel (Ville de Toulouse), 1968-1974; 6 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Centre de Documentation de La Musique Contemporaine (CDMC), 1981-1996, no date; 21 (Box 26, Folder 12)
      See also Instituut voor Psychoacustica
    - Centre Georges Pompidou [and IRCAM], 1976-1998; 17 (Box 26, Folder 12)
      See also Illouz, Gabriel (1977)
    - Centre International d'Etudes Pedagogiques (CIDE), 1976; 2 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Centre Leo Lagrangre (Concours Renaissance des Orgues), 1977; 2 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Centre National d'Action Musicale (CENAM), 1984; 1 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Centre National de la Cinématographie, 1985-1986; 4 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Centre National de la Recherche Scientifique, 1987; 1 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - C.G. Bjurström (Publishers), 1958; 2 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Chafeaux, Jean-Pierre, 1989; 2 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Chamber Music Society of Lincoln Center, 1974-1977; 4 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      See also Theodore Presser Company; Wadsworth, Charles
    - Chambers, Donald (first cousin once removed), 1986; 1 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Chambers, Maria (daughter of Donald; 1st cousin twice rem.), 2000; 2 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - de Chambure, Alain, 1991; 1 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Chamfray, Claude, 1967, no date; 5 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Chang, Dorothy, 1998; 1 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Chapelle Musicale Reine Elisabeth, 2000; 3 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Chappuis, Martiné, 1995; 2 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Char, Réne, 1962-1975; 3 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Charles Ives Centennial Festival-Conference, 1974; 9 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      See also Perlis, Vivian
    - Charlston, Elsa, 1976; 2 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Charpentier, Jacques
      See Le Ministère de la Culture
    - Charrié, Etienne, 2001; 3 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - La Chartreuse (CIRCA), 1991; 2 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      See also Ducol, Bruno
    - Chassaigne, Claire, 1991-1992; 2 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Chassin, Claire, 1988; 3 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Chaster, Adrian and Libby (née Jolas, 1st cousin once removed), 1993; 2 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Châtelet, Theatre Musical de Paris, 1992; 1 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Chateauroux, Ville de, 2001; 1 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Chattaway, Bill and Deborah, 1998, no date; 12 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Chaynes, Charles, 1972-1986; 12 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Chen, Qigang, 1987-1996; 7 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      See also Messiaen, Olivier
    - Cheng, Gloria, 1992; 2 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Cheng, M., 1995; 1 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Chéreau, Patrice, 1989; 1 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Chevalier, Jeanne, 2007; 2 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Le Chevallier, Nicolette, 1968-1973; 3 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Le Chevallier, Dr. Paul L., 1968; 1 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Chimènes, Myriam, 2003; 1 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      See also Centre National de la Recherche Scientifique
    - Chirac, Jacques, 1981; 3 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      See also Paris, Ville de; Présidence de la République
    - Chiti, Patricia Adkins, 1992-1995; 3 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Chmoulevitch, Vsevolod, No date; 2 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Choeur Contemporain
      See Hayrabedian, Roland
    - Choeur de Chambre de Strasbourg, 2002; 1 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Choisir pour la reconnaissance du droit des femmes
      See Dulong, Anny
    - Chojnacka, Elizabeth, 1993; 2 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Christie, William
      See Les Arts Florissants
    - Cipollone, Maria, 1985; 1 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Circolo Degli Artisti
      See Di Lotti, Silvana
    - La Cité de la Musique, 2005; 1 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      See also Hondre, Emmanuel
    - Cité des Arts, 1977; 2 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Claoué, Yves, 1971; 2 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Clark, Susan and Jim, 1999; 1 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Clark University, 1993-1994; 6 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Class, Olivier, 1999; 1 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - ?, Claude [La Rol?], 1979; 2 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - ?, Claude, 1989; 1 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Claude, Cécile, 1991; 1 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Classic (Groupe Master Press), 1991; 1 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Claverie, J. P., No date; 1 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Clavreul, Robin, 1996; 1 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Clingan, Alton Howe, 1995; 3 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Clementi, Aldo, 1990; 1 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Clostre, Adrienne, 1993; 1 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Cobey, Patricia
      See Léandre, Joëlle
    - Cochereau, No date; 1 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Cogan, Robert, 1995; 1 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Cohen, Aaron I., 1974-1981; 2 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Cohen, Jeff, No date; 1 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Cohen, Jean, 1993; 1 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Cohen, Roger and Frieda, 1948-2000; 2 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Cohen-Levinas, Danielle, 1989-1998, no date; 16 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      See also D'un Opéra de Voyage; L'Itineraire
    - Colem, Liz, 1996; 1 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      See also Bennington College
    - Collaer, Paul, 1970; 2 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Collège Claude Delvincourt, 1988; 2 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Collège International de Philosophie, 1991; 1 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      See also L'Itineraire
    - College Philosophique, 1967; 2 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Collot, Serge, 1966-2003, no date; 14 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Colorado Music Festival, 1979-1989; 8 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      See also Bernstein, Giora; Boosey & Hawkes; University of Colorado
    - Columbia University, 1984-1998; 2 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      See also Theodore Presser Company; Trawick, Eleanor
    - Combes, Jean René, 1985-1989; 6 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Comes, Robert, 1995; 2 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Comité National Victor Hugo, 1983; 1 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Comité d'Organisation des Assises Nationales de la Musique, 1982; 1 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Commission Franco-Américaine d'Échanges, 1979-1987; 2 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Comoy, Colette, 1985-1986; 2 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Composer's Forum Inc., 1973-1988; 12 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Composers Recordings, Inc. (CRI), 1973-1995; 12 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Composer-to-Composer, 1989; 1 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Les Concerts de Saint Cloud, 1979; 1 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Concord String Quartet, 1973-1974; 6 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      See also The Kindler Foundation; Theodore Presser Company
    - Concours de Composition Henri Dutilleux, 1989-1996; 3 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Concours International de Composition Musicale de Genève, 1989; 3 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Concours International Jean-Marie Londeix, 1995; 1 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Condé, Gerard, 1987-2006; 6 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Confédération des Travailleurs Intellectuels de France (CTI), 1975; 1 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Conseil des Arts du Canada, 1996; 1 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Conseil Superieur de l'Audiovisuel, 1989; 1 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Conservatoire de Boulogne, 1986-1987; 2 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Conservatoire "Gustave Charpentier" (Ville de Paris), 1987; 1 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Conservatoire Municipal du Centre de Paris W.A. Mozart, No date; 2 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      See also Poindefert, Bruno
    - Conservatoire Municipal Olivier Messiaen (Ris-Orangis)
      See Gaussin, Allain
    - Conservatoire National de Région - Montpellier District, 1994; 1 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Conservatoire National de Région - Paris, 1993; 2 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Conservatoire National de Région - Ville d'Amiens, 1986; 2 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Conservatoire National de Région - Ville de Dijon, 1989-1990; 6 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Conservatoire National de Région - Ville de Limoges, 1987, no date; 3 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Conservatoire National de Région - Ville de Nice, 1983; 1 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Conservatoire National de Région - Ville de Toulouse, 1985-1986; 4 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Conservatoire National Supérieur de Musique de Lyon (CNSML), 1985-1993; 3 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      See also Amy, Gilbert; Lamy, Anne-Marie
    - Conservatoire National Supérieur de Musique de Paris (CNSMP), 1970-2001, no date; 46 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      See also Conservatoire National de Région - Paris; Dupin, Marc-Olivier; Louvrier, Alain; L'Ordre National du Mérite; Poirier, Alain; Trachier, Olivier
    - Conservatoire Royal de Musique de Liège, 1980-1984; 3 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      See also Pousseur, Henri
    - Conservatori Superior Municipal de Música (Barcelona), 1989-1991; 5 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      See also Helffer, Claude
    - Conservatorio Statale di Musica "Giuseppe Verdi", 1990; 1 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Conséquences, 1984-1985; 3 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Constant, Marius, 1981; 2 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Consulat Général de France - San Francisco, No date; 2 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Conte, Michel, 1984; 1 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Contet, Henri, 1974-1975; 2 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      See also Société des Auteurs, Compositerus et Éditeurs
    - Cooper, Dan, 1998; 1 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Copland, Aaron, 1991; 1 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Copley, William and Noma (Foundation), 1955-1956; 4 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - de Coppet, Véronique (née Limon), 1993-1997; 14 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Coquillat, Michelle
      See Ministère des droits de la femme
    - Corbett, Sidney (Sid), 1991; 2 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Corda Quartett, 1995; 2 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Cornu, Laurence, 1991; 3 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Cosserat, Dr. Thierry, 1994; 2 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Costère, Edmond (Coester, Edouard), 1983; 2 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Coulais, Bruno, 1988 [?]; 1 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Courand, Marcel, 1973; 2 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Couroupos, Georges, 1998; 1 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Le Courrier Musical de France
      See Chamfray, Claude
    - Coury, Michel, 1978-1983; 22 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Couteau, Cati, 1990-2006, no date; 5 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Crockett, Donald
      See University of Southern California
    - Crossley, Aline, No date; 2 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Crudeli, Marcella, 1990; 1 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Crumb, George, 1976-2005; 35 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      See also Colorado Music Festival; American Academy of Arts and Letters
    - Csaba, Peter
      See Orchestre de Besançon
    - Curtil, Yvette, 1995; 1 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Curtis Institute
      See Nelson, Philip F.; Theodore Presser Company
    - Cyclope (Theatre du?), 2005; 1 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Cyrn, Denise, No date; 2 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Dachy, Marc, 1987; 1 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - von Daalen, Marylea, 2002; 2 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - van Daele, Christine, 2007; 1 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Dagnicourt, Jean, 1992, no date; 2 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Dalbavie, Marc-André, 1990, no date; 2 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Damian, Jean-Michel, 1991; 2 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - D'Amico, Anne Marie, 1986; 5 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Daniel, Alain, 1980; 2 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Darasse, Xavier, 1971-1989, no date; 6 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      See also Anders, Mariedi; Les Arts Renaißants
    - Darbon, Nicolas, 1994-1995; 6 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Darmon, Jean-Pierre, 1986; 2 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Daroux, Cécile, No date; 1 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Dartigolles, J.B., No date; 2 (Box 27, Folder 8)